Over ten years ago,
a series of gates linking our world
to an alternate dimension appeared.
The other side of each gate teemed
with bizarre creatures called "magic beasts,"
immune to conventional weaponry.
Those who have awakened the abilities
necessary to fight these beasts
are called hunters.
Based on the amount of magical power
contained within their bodies,
they are ranked, in descending order,
as S, A, B, C, D, or E-Rank.
However, once these powers have awakened,
no amount of individual effort
can ever result in greater strength.
The one who awoke to the weakest level
of strength, even among the E-Ranks,
was me, Sung Jinwoo.
Having become "The Weakest Hunter of
All Mankind," I was always a hindrance,
and always on the verge of death.
There are only a handful of
S-Rank hunters in the country.
I wish I could've been like them.
And overseeing those hunters,
as well as managing dungeon raids,
is the Hunter's Association.
They're unfathomably strong.
And they fight together.
People who help each other,
are useful, and support each other.
The kind of person that someone as
helpless and useless as I could never be.
That's what I thought...
until everything changed.
Hey, it's Sung!
What's up, Sung?
I'm Sung Jinwoo, and even among
the weakest of all ranks,
Nice of you to come out despite
the chilly weather.
I had earned a certain nickname...
His nickname is "The Weakest
Hunter of All Mankind."
But even if I was the weakest of all mankind,
I had a family to protect.
Let's give it our best.
Today, I'm gonna see this through!
I needed to help beat the dungeons on the
other side of the gates and earn a living.
I did it!
I finally got one.
Jinwoo!
Stay back, Joohee!
You're going to be okay!
I promise I'll heal you!
All right!
That's Mr. Song for you!
Hey!
Take a look at this!
After clearing the dungeon, further in,
we discovered it was a double dungeon—
I'm in!
I say no.
if we took on the risk, we'd have the chance
to earn even greater rewards.
No.
I'm the only one who can
provide for my family.
We took a vote, and the majority
decided to keep going.
Let's go.
And that was a mistake.
Everybody, get down!
What is happening here?
How is this possible?
We're trapped. We're done for.
We're dead. Dead.
We're gonna die!
We were absolutely helpless against
the boss of the double dungeon.
I can't... I can't do this!
I can't die just yet!
We had no choice but to wait for death.
I wanna make it home alive!
Mr. Song. Take Joohee and go.
I just said I'm going to stay—
Then who's going to carry Joohee out?
There's no time. Hurry!
You can't, Jinwoo!
In that case, it should be me—
I promised to take you out to eat, didn't I?
Use this to buy yourself dinner.
And when I get out of here,
I'll be along to collect the change.
How can you even say—
I'm sorry. But it looks like
we really are out of time.
Please.
Good. I'm the only one who has to die.
I'll take at least one of you down with me...
So bring it on!
I've always been the weakest.
And I've been mocked for it,
time and time again.
But I've always tried as hard as I could.
And now...
This is bullshit.
It's bullshit! This is such bullshit!
I tried to be stronger...
but I couldn't.
And even then,
I gave it my all to get this far!
You couldn't take any more?
We all felt the same way!
All you were doing was
justifying your own selfishness!
That gratitude was purely superficial.
It's always the most selfish
people who benefit the most!
I have a family, too!
I wanted to make it home alive, too!
It's good that I'm the only one
who has to die?
How could you think that,
you stupid hypocrite?
No. I don't wanna die.
If... If I had one more chance...
When I woke up, I was in a hospital bed,
A hospital?
and the limbs that I had lost were back
like nothing had happened.
My arm's intact.
My legs, too.
And that wasn't the only strange thing.
For some reason, there were these things
like message windows from a game
But, Jinah... Can you see this?
that only I could see.
See what?
Never mind. Sorry.
It's been four days since
I regained consciousness.
I've figured out a few things.
First, I'm not hallucinating these windows.
When I complete the daily quest,
I get three types of rewards.
Full recovery.
All that exhaustion is gone in a flash.
Next is the ability points.
I can distribute the points
into whatever abilities I choose.
I should probably go with strength, right?
Upgrading my abilities makes me
that much more powerful.
I can literally tell that
I've got more strength now.
And my final daily quest reward...
the random loot box.
I wonder what it'll be today?
A key?
An instance dungeon? What's that?
Based on what's happened so far, it'll be
some kind of event to help me get stronger...
What do I do? I'm suddenly
feeling less confident.
Here they come! And there's three!
I beat one...
It doesn't look anything
like the station I know.
So fast!
The sword...
Even after all that leveling up,
its name is still...
orange?
If it lands a clean hit on me, I'm dead.
I thought I'd gotten a bit stronger...
Is it still not enough?
How much stronger do I need to get...
before it makes up for a life
spent being a laughing stock?
I've...
gotta get stronger!
Not yet!
Compared to that thing...
Compared to the terror I felt back then...
This will be easy!
I focused specifically
on increasing my strength!
I should be able to...
I know that, here and now,
I can kill you!
Oh my gosh, did you see him?
After awakening, your ability
values are set and don't change.
I sure did! You mean the E-Rank, right?
But for some reason...
I'm the only person that can level up.
Excuse me.
Mr. Sung Jinwoo...
Oh, sorry.
And you seem taller.
Did the exercise help with that, too?
This would help me earn
way more money than before.
I guess men keep growing
even when they're adults!
Or so I thought...
That said... It's not exactly easy, either.
To make good money, I need to go
through higher-ranked gates.
But no one's gonna let an
E-Rank hunter into those.
Maybe I could get re-appraised?
A higher rank could get me into better gates,
and maybe a bit of attention
will help me earn more...
I'd definitely stand out, though.
Re-awakenings are rare enough.
I've never heard of a hunter who could
level up and keep getting stronger.
Which would probably mean even more scrutiny.
The press would eat it up... and there's
the saying about the nail that sticks out.
I better not.
Not until I can properly defend myself
and learn what the deal is with this power.
Confirm.
Hey, there!
I'm Hwang Dongsuk.
Sung Jinwoo.
You're E-Rank, right?
Right.
It looks like we're here for the same reason.
I'm Yoo Jinho. Twenty-one years old, D-Rank.
I'm here to meet the quota, too.
A D-Rank with gear like that?
This kid's family must be rich.
Is this your first time in a C-Rank dungeon?
It's okay! I'll keep you safe.
Let's be on our way!
Good! Now, let's wrap this up!
Hell yeah!
They're well coordinated.
It's easy to see that they've been
working together for a long time.
Still, it might be the lack of a healer,
but they're a bit rough around the edges.
Something...
feels off.
Kyuhwan... seal off the boss chamber.
My hunch was right.
A seasoned party that needed
extra members to meet the quota...
The entrance! But why?
One with no healers.
Hwang Dongsuk had been hiring low-ranked
hunters to meet the entrance quota,
and then killing them in the dungeon
to monopolize the rewards.
Their plan was to trap me and Jinho
in the boss chamber and let us die.
But because I beat the boss,
their plan was in shambles.
So they tried to kill us.
Enemies...
The system is telling me to kill.
The system wants me alive.
It wants me strong.
I'd forgotten.
The weak always get taken from.
That's how it works here.
Hey, look! The Weakest Hunter
of All Mankind actually gets it!
That means you guys understand
how it works, too, right?
How what works?
If you're hunters...
then you're ready to be
preyed on yourselves, right?
Let me handle this, Mr. Dongsuk.
Look, buddy. You clearly don't
understand what's going on here.
We should be ready to be preyed on?
And what's a jumped-up
E-Rank like you gonna do?
The Weakest Hunter of All—
I just killed someone.
A human being.
Even if I was just obeying the system,
I've... just murdered another person.
But if I hadn't done it, I would've died.
So I can't back down now.
If only the strong get to survive, then...!
Go to hell!
How's an E-Rank got moves like that?
Son of a bitch...
Take this!
He's so strong...
He feels stronger now than when
he was fighting the dungeon boss.
H-He took my entire team apart in seconds...
Was he hiding his true strength?
You beat the boss, didn't you?
Well, I might be a C-Rank, too,
but you'll find I'm nothing like them!
Reinforcement!
Mr. Hwang. You're strong.
But I've got some bad news for you.
I've been leveling up this entire time.
Wh-What just happened?
He... He smashed me into the ground?
There's no way in hell he's E-Rank!
H-Hang on! Don't kill me!
You've gotta show mercy! I-I can pay you!
The mana crystals and essence stones...
You can have the lot!
I-Is that not enough for you?
I-In that case...
I'll pay you double! Double what I was—
Three times.
You tried to kill me three times...
and now you want mercy?
D-Don't do it!
Y-You won't get away with this!
Weren't you the one who said nothing
that happens in a dungeon ever gets out?
You little shit! Do you have
any idea who my brother—
I've become strong.
For the people I love, I'll make
any sacrifice to get stronger.
Whether it's against magic beasts or humans,
I can't stop fighting.
I have to keep...
leveling up.